A Guide to the Asia Society records FA110
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Performing Arts Department, Director, Beate Gordon Files, 1961-1986; 6
  - General Files, 5
    - Fundraising, 1980 (Box 508, Folder 5332)
    - Grants, 1973-1980 (Box 508, Folder 5333)
    - Beate Gordon - Biographical, 1977 (Box 508, Folder 5334)
    - Childyear Culture Corps Project, 1978 (Box 508, Folder 5335)
    - Jay Hoffman - Children's Program Proposal, 1980 (Box 508, Folder 5336)
    - Contacts - Japan, 1979 (Box 508, Folder 5337)
    - Japan Foundation, 1973-1976, 1978 (Box 508, Folder 5338)
    - Liang Tsai-Ping Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 508, Folder 5339)
    - Masks - Photos, 1981 July 8 (Box 508, Folder 5340)
    - Nonesuch Music Project, 1978-1979 (Box 508, Folder 5341)
    - Nonesuch Music Project, 1976-1980 (Box 508, Folder 5342)
    - Nonesuch Music Project - Teresa Sterne, no date (Box 508, Folder 5343)
    - Nonesuch Music Project - Financial (Box 509, Folder 5344)
    - Nonesuch Music Project - Royalties, 1977-1978 (Box 509, Folder 5345)
    - Troupes (former Isadora Bennett Program), 1961-1964 (Box 509, Folder 5346)
    - Performing Arts Program (PAP) - Publicity, 1961-1964 (Box 509, Folder 5347)
    - Press Release - Re: TV Broadcast (Box 509, Folder 5348)
    - Puppet Congress, 1979-1980 (Box 509, Folder 5349)
    - Radio and TV Spots, 1976-1979 (Box 509, Folder 5350)
    - Kathakali Spots, 1981 (Box 509, Folder 5351)
    - Rennes, 1978-1979 (Box 509, Folder 5352)
    - Films - Asian Theater Program (Box 509, Folder 5353)
    - Earlham Oberlin video, film resources, 1975-1976 (Box 509, Folder 5354)
    - Resources of the Asian Dance Collection - Performing Arts Research Center, Lincoln Center (Box 509, Folder 5355)
    - Resource Materials (Box 509, Folder 5356)
    - Correspondence - Programs, 1975-1979 (Box 510, Folder 5357)
    - Future Troupes - Japan, 1978-1979 (Box 510, Folder 5358)
    - Programs - Video and TV, 1972-1980 (Box 510, Folder 5359-5360)
    - Bhutan film - Australia and New Zealand, 1980-1981 (Box 510, Folder 5361)
    - NEH Grant, 1975-1977 (Box 510, Folder 5362)
    - Toyota Grant - Final Proposal, 1978 (Box 510, Folder 5363)
    - National Endorsement For the Arts - Dance Program, 1975-1978 (Box 510, Folder 5364)
    - Grant Materials, 1977-1978 (Box 511, Folder 5365)
    - Video evaluations (Box 511, Folder 5366)
    - Foreign TV Stations, 1977-1980 (Box 511, Folder 5367)
    - Future Troupes - China, 1979-1980 (Box 511, Folder 5368)
    - China Trip, 1979 (Box 511, Folder 5369)
    - Bandit Princess, 1980 (Box 511, Folder 5370)
    - New Troupes - Booking, 1978-1979 (Box 511, Folder 5371)
    - Book Review Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 511, Folder 5372)
    - Japan, 1978 (Box 511, Folder 5373)
    - Carnegie Hall Contracts and Arrangements, 1976-1980 (Box 511, Folder 5374)
    - Chinese Photo Exhibit, 1980 (Box 511, Folder 5375)
    - Bhutan Reception, 1980 (Box 511, Folder 5376)
    - ASEAN, 1976-1979 (Box 512, Folder 5377)
    - Asian Ambassadors to U.S., 1980-1981 (Box 512, Folder 5378)
    - Asian Representatives to the United Nations, 1980 (Box 512, Folder 5379)
    - Asian Foundation, 1977 (Box 512, Folder 5380)
    - Performing Arts Department - Program Sheet, 1980 February-May (Box 512, Folder 5381)
    - Performing Arts Department - Fact Sheets and Annual Reports, 1971-1976 (Box 512, Folder 5382)
    - Performing Arts Program - Advisory Committee Meeting, 1972 April 27 (Box 512, Folder 5383)
    - Performing Arts Program - Advisory Committee Meeting, 1970 (Box 512, Folder 5384)
    - Lockwood Report (Box 512, Folder 5385)
    - Wallace-Mellon Pressbook and Preface, 1976-1977 (Box 512, Folder 5386)
    - Performing Arts Program - Report, 1980 (Box 512, Folder 5387)
    - Chinese Brochures (Box 512, Folder 5388)
    - Japanese Brochures (Box 512, Folder 5389)
    - Southeast Asia (Box 512, Folder 5390)
    - Korean Brochures (Box 512, Folder 5391)
    - Brochures of Other Organizations, 1981-1983 (Box 512, Folder 5392)
    - Brochures of Other Organizations, 1981-1983 (Box 513, Folder 5393)
    - Revlon Kimono Exhibit (Cancelled), 1982 August (Box 513, Folder 5394)
    - Korean Craft Art Exhibition, 1982 August-September (Box 513, Folder 5395)
    - SUNY - Arts on TV, 1982 (Box 513, Folder 5396)
    - Renwick Gallery Project (Smithsonian), 1982 (Box 513, Folder 5397)
    - Asian American Dance Theater, 1982 (Box 513, Folder 5398)
    - Samul-Nori, 1983 November (Box 516, Folder 5413)
    - Okinawa Tour, 1981 (Box 516, Folder 5414)
    - Committee Discussions, 1985 (Box 516, Folder 5415)
    - Brochures and Publications, 1986 (Box 516, Folder 5416)
    - Performing Arts Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 516, Folder 5417)
    - Videotape Project, 1979 (Box 516, Folder 5418)
    - Complimentary Letters, 1971-1979 (Box 516, Folder 5419)
  - Peforming Arts Program Financial Ledgers, 6
    - Performing Arts Program - Ledgers, Budgets, undated, 1970-1971, 1971-1972 (Box 517, Folder 5420)
      Restricted from scholarly access - Financial Material
    - Performing Arts Program - Ledgers, Budgets, 1972-1973, 1973-1974, 1974-1975 (Box 517, Folder 5421)
    - Performing Arts Program - Ledgers, Budgets, 1976-1977, 1977-1978 (Box 518, Folder 5422)
    - Performing Arts Program - Ledgers, Budgets, 1978-1979, 1979-1980 (Box 518, Folder 5423)
- Asia Society President, Robert B. Oxnam Files, 1982-1987; 7
  Series 7: Asia Society President, Robert B. Oxnam Files
  Subseries 1: Departmental Files
  Subseries 2: Chronological File
  See also: Series 11.
  - Departmental Files, 1
    - Galleries, 1986 (Box 519, Folder 5424)
    - Peformance, Lectures, Films, 1986 (Box 519, Folder 5425)
    - Performing Arts, 1986 (Box 519, Folder 5426)
    - Public Relations, 1986-1987 (Box 519, Folder 5427)
    - Public Relations, Publications, 1986 (Box 519, Folder 5428)
    - Public Relations, Publications, 1986 (Box 520, Folder 5429)
    - Public Relations, 1986 (Box 520, Folder 5430)
    - Houston Center, 1986 (Box 520, Folder 5431)
    - Washington DC Center, 1986 (Box 520, Folder 5432)
    - Los Angeles Center, 1986 (Box 520, Folder 5433)
    - Department Heads Meeting, 1986 November 25 (Box 521, Folder 5434)
    - Department Heads Meeting, 1986 June 10 (Box 521, Folder 5435)
    - Department Heads Meeting, 1986 May 6 (Box 521, Folder 5436)
    - Department Heads Meeting, 1986 April 1 (Box 521, Folder 5437)
    - Full Staff Meeting, 1986 December 19 (Box 521, Folder 5438)
    - Staff Meeting Picnic, 1986 June 25 (Box 521, Folder 5439)
    - Festival of India 1985, 1984 (Box 521, Folder 5440)
    - The Asia Society Fact Sheets and Interview with Robert B. Oxman, 1987 (Box 521, Folder 5441)
    - Art of Japan, 1986-1987 (Box 521, Folder 5442)
    - John Thomson Photo Exhibition, 1986 (Box 521, Folder 5443)
    - Programs - General, 1986 (Box 521, Folder 5444)
    - Performing Arts, Films, 1986 (Box 521, Folder 5445)
    - 30th Anniversary Queries, 1986 (Box 521, Folder 5446)
    - Galleries - General, 1986 (Box 521, Folder 5447)
    - Asia Society Open House, 1986 (Box 521, Folder 5448)
    - 30th Anniversary Gala Dinner, 1986 (Box 521, Folder 5449)
    - Buddhist Book Illuminations, 1987 (Box 521, Folder 5450)
    - Chinese Painting Demostration, 1986 (Box 521, Folder 5451)
    - Chinese Scholars Studio, 1986 (Box 521, Folder 5452)
    - Far East America Council of Commerce and Industry, 1982-1986 (Box 521, Folder 5453)
    - Contemporary Affairs, 1986 (Box 522, Folder 5454)
    - Contemporary Affairs, 1986 (Box 522, Folder 5455)
    - Contemporary Affairs, 1986 (Box 522, Folder 5456)
    - Public Affairs, 1986 (Box 522, Folder 5457)
    - Public Affairs, 1986 (Box 523, Folder 5458)
    - Development, 1986 (Box 523, Folder 5459)
    - Development, 1986 (Box 523, Folder 5460)
    - Finance and Administration, 1986-1987 (Box 523, Folder 5461)
    - Finance and Administration, 1986 (Box 524, Folder 5462)
    - Education and Communication, 1986 (Box 524, Folder 5463)
    - Publications and Public Relations - Encyclopedia of Asian History, 1986-1987 (Box 524, Folder 5464)
    - Finance and Administration, 1986 (Box 524, Folder 5465)
    - Finance and Administration, 1986 (Box 524, Folder 5466)
    - Galleries, 1986 (Box 525, Folder 5467)
    - Galleries, 1986 (Box 525, Folder 5468)
  - Chronological File, 2
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1983 April-May (Box 544, Folder 5611)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1983 June (Box 544, Folder 5612)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1983 July (Box 544, Folder 5613)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1983 August (Box 544, Folder 5614)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1983 September (Box 544, Folder 5615)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1983 October (Box 545, Folder 5616)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1983 November (Box 545, Folder 5617)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1983 December (Box 545, Folder 5618)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1984 January (Box 545, Folder 5619)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1984 February (Box 545, Folder 5620)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1984 March (Box 545, Folder 5621)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1984 April (Box 546, Folder 5622)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1984 May (Box 546, Folder 5623)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1984 June (Box 546, Folder 5624)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1984 July (Box 546, Folder 5625)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1984 August (Box 546, Folder 5626)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1984 September (Box 546, Folder 5627)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1984 October (Box 547, Folder 5628)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1984 November (Box 547, Folder 5629-5630)
    - RBO - Chronological File, 1984 December (Box 547, Folder 5630A)
- Public Affairs, 1966-1986; 8
  Series 8: Public Affairs
  Subseries 1: Asian Development Seminar Program (ADSP) – General Files
  Subseries 2: Director of Public Affairs, Marshall M. Bouton (MMB) Files
  Subseries 3: Public Affairs Day File
  Subseries 4: ADSP – Authors, Institutions and Audio Tapes.
  Subseries 5: ADSP – Seminar Reports and Background papers
  Subseries 6: ADSP – Ethical Dilemmas of Development in Asia
  Subseries 7: Inaugural papers
  Subseries 8: Worker Migration Studies
  See also: Series 1 and Series 2.
  - Asian Development Seminar Program (ADSP) - General Files, 1
    - MARIO "American Sketchbook" Exhibit (Cartoonist), 1975 (Box 876, Folder 5469)
    - ADSP Correspondence 1981 - Meetings and Studies (Box 525, Folder 5470)
    - AID Sustaining Grant-1219 - Contract and Accounting, 1981 (Box 525, Folder 5471)
    - Grant ASB-0249-G-SS-1058-00, 1981-1982 (Box 525, Folder 5472)
    - Grant ASB-0249-G-SS-2011-00, 1981-1982 (Box 525, Folder 5473)
    - Background, 1980 (Box 525, Folder 5474)
    - "Smallholder Tree Farming Project" - Project Completion Report, 1981 (Box 526, Folder 5475)
    - Forestry in National Development: Production systems, conservation, foreign trade and AID, 1979 (Box 526, Folder 5476)
    - Principles and practice in watershed development projects, 1981 (Box 526, Folder 5477)
    - Effective policies and legislative needs for stimultaing growth through community forestry in forest based economies within an agrarian environment - The Case of India, 1981 (Box 526, Folder 5478)
    - SEADAG Papers - Correspondence, 1977 February-June (Box 526, Folder 5479)
    - SEADAG - Day File, 1976 July-August (Box 526, Folder 5480)
    - SEADAG - Day File, 1976 September-November (Box 526, Folder 5481)
    - ADSP - Day File, 1976 December-1977 January (Box 526, Folder 5482)
    - ADSP - Day File, 1977 February-April (Box 527, Folder 5483)
    - ADSP - Day File, 1979 May-July (Box 527, Folder 5484)
    - ADSP - Day File, 1979 June-December (Box 527, Folder 5485)
    - ADSP, 1979-1980 (Box 527, Folder 5486)
    - ADSP - Day File, 1980 January-February (Box 527, Folder 5487)
    - ADSP - Day File, 1980 September-December (Box 527, Folder 5488)
    - ADSP - Day File, 1981 April-June (Box 528, Folder 5489)
    - ADSP - Day File, 1981 July-August (Box 528, Folder 5490)
    - ADSP - Day File, 1981 September-November (Box 528, Folder 5491)
    - ADSP - Day File, 1981 December-1982 January (Box 529, Folder 5492)
    - ADSP - Day File, 1982 February (Box 529, Folder 5493)
    - ADSP - Day File, 1982 March (Box 529, Folder 5494)
    - ADSP - Day File, 1982 April (Box 529, Folder 5495)
    - Forestry Conference Correspondence, 1982 March-April (Box 530, Folder 5496)
    - Forestry Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 530, Folder 5497)
    - Forestry Conference papers, 1981-1982 (Box 530, Folder 5498-5500)
    - SEADAG 75-1 - James C. Scott paper - "Exploration in Rural Class Relations", 1975 (Box 531, Folder 5501)
    - ADSP, 1981 (Box 531, Folder 5502)
    - ADSP Activity Report, 1977-1980 (Box 531, Folder 5503)
    - ADSP Activities, 1979-1980 (Box 531, Folder 5504)
    - Herbert D. Spivack (HDS) - Conferences and Seminars, 1977-1979 (Box 531, Folder 5505)
      Herbert D. Spivack, Director of Meetings and Studies Program.
    - Herbert D. Spivack (HDS) - Conferences and Seminars, 1979 (Box 531, Folder 5506)
    - Herbert D. Spivack (HDS) - Conferences and Seminars, 1980 (Box 531, Folder 5507)
    - Herbert D. Spivack (HDS) - Meetings and Studies - Public Affairs Daily Events Sheets, 1976-1981 (Box 532, Folder 5508)
    - Herbert D. Spivack (HDS) - Meetings and Studies - Monthly Events, 1972-1977 (Box 532, Folder 5509)
    - Herbert D. Spivack (HDS) - Meetings and Studies - Monthly Events, 1977 June-1978 June (Box 532, Folder 5510)
    - Herbert D. Spivack (HDS) - Meetings and Studies - Monthly Events, 1978 July-1980 June (Box 532, Folder 5511)
    - Herbert D. Spivack (HDS) - Chronological Files, 1980 January-June (Box 532, Folder 5512)
    - Herbert D. Spivack (HDS) - Chronological Files, 1980 July-1981 June (Box 532, Folder 5513)
      Folders 5514 and 5515 not used.
    - Herbert D. Spivack (HDS) - Programs, 1980 (Box 533, Folder 5516)
    - Herbert D. Spivack (HDS) - Programs, 1980 (Box 533, Folder 5517)
    - Herbert D. Spivack (HDS) - Programs, 1980-1981 (Box 533, Folder 5518)
    - Programs, 1981 (Box 533, Folder 5519)
    - Herbert D. Spivack (HDS) - ADSP Seminar Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 533, Folder 5520)
    - HDS - Asia Toward the Year 2000 Sessions, 1981 (Box 533, Folder 5521)
    - Publicity for Meetings and Seminars (Box 533, Folder 5522)
    - Country Councils - Chairpersons, 1981 (Box 533, Folder 5523)
    - Afghanistan Council - Newsletter, 1981 (Box 533, Folder 5524)
    - Training Asian Development Administrators Conference, 1981 (Box 534, Folder 5525)
    - AID Per Diem Rates - Foreign Travel (Box 534, Folder 5526)
    - General Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 534, Folder 5527)
    - Inagural Events, 1981 (Box 534, Folder 5528)
    - Asian Labor Migration Workshop, 1981 (Box 534, Folder 5529)
    - Cheryl A. Solometo (CAS) - Chronological File, 1981 (Box 534, Folder 5530)
    - SEADAG Directory, 1968-1969 (Box 534, Folder 5531)
    - Petty Cash, 1973-1974 (Box 535, Folder 5532)
    - Ledger 1975-1976 and Seminar Costs (Box 535, Folder 5533)
    - Asia: 2000 Ledger, 1981 (Box 535, Folder 5534)
    - Audiotape - Asia: 2000, no date (Box 535, Folder 5535)
    - Training development administrators in Asia - next generation, 1981 (Box 536, Folder 5536)
    - Forestry Development in Asia, 1978 (Box 536, Folder 5537)
    - ADSP - Day File, 1982 May (Box 536, Folder 5538)
    - Asian Ambassadors to U.S (D.C.), 1981 (Box 536, Folder 5539)
    - Invitations to Programs, 1976 (Box 536, Folder 5540)
    - SEADAG - Replies, 1981-1982 (Box 536, Folder 5541)
    - List of SEADAG Papers and Reports, 1971 (Box 536A, Folder 5542)
    - 1980 - Asia House Activities, fall programs and misc. (Box 536A, Folder 5543)
    - Training Asian Development Administrators Conference, 1980 (Box 536A, Folder 5544)
    - Oxnam Day File, 1979-1981 (Box 536A, Folder 5545)
    - ADSP-Asia Society Correspondence, 1981 (Box 536A, Folder 5546)
    - Generational change in Asia Project, 1981 (Box 536A, Folder 5547)
    - Public affairs department, 1981 (Box 536A, Folder 5548)
    - Ted Tanen - ADSP Programming, 1981 (Box 536A, Folder 5549)
    - Phillips Talbot, 1978-1981 (Box 536A, Folder 5550)
    - Congressional Human Rights Acts, UN Declaration of Human Rights, 1977 (Box 536A, Folder 5551)
    - Public Law 480 project, 1979 (Box 536A, Folder 5552)
    - Halligan File, 1981 (Box 536A, Folder 5553)
    - Program Planning: AID Washington, 1981 (Box 536A, Folder 5554)
    - Future Activities, 1981 (Box 536A, Folder 5555)
    - Asia Bureau - AID Irregular Papers, 1980 (Box 536A, Folder 5556)
    - ADSP - Day File, 1982 June (Box 536A, Folder 5557)
    - Human Rights Seminar - Accounting, 1980-1981 (Box 537, Folder 5558)
    - Stability and Security in Souteast Asia, 1982 (Box 537, Folder 5559)
    - Agency for International Development (AID), 1977-1982 (Box 537, Folder 5560)
    - ADSP Annual Report, 1976-1977, Activity Report 1979 (Box 538, Folder 5561)
    - Ethics II - Project Proposal, 1981-1982 (Box 538, Folder 5562)
  - Director of Public Affairs, Marshall M. Bouton (MMB) Files, 2
    - Letters to Members, 1981 (Box 538, Folder 5563)
    - Asia: 2000, 1981 (Box 538, Folder 5564-5568)
    - Asia: 2000 - Background Material, 1981 (Box 539, Folder 5569-5570)
    - Asia: 2000 - Accounting, 1981 (Box 539, Folder 5571-5572)
    - Asia: 2000 - Report, 1981-1982 (Box 539, Folder 5573)
    - Asia 2000 - Rockefeller Foundation Grant Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 539, Folder 5574)
    - Asia: 2000 - Contemporary Southeast Asia Report, 1982 (Box 539, Folder 5575)
    - Asia: 2000 - Planning Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 539, Folder 5576)
    - Asia: 2000 - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 540, Folder 5577)
    - Asia: 2000 - Papers, 1981 (Box 540, Folder 5578)
    - Asia: 2000, 1981 (Box 540, Folder 5579)
    - Asian Development Seminar program (ADSP), 1981-1982 (Box 541, Folder 5580)
    - ADSP - Background material, 1981-1982 (Box 541, Folder 5581)
    - ADSP- Ethical Dilemma of Development - Publication, 1981-1982 (Box 541, Folder 5582)
    - ADSP - Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 541, Folder 5583)
    - Program associate - ADSP, 1981-1982 (Box 541, Folder 5584)
    - Marshall M. Bouton (MMB) - Chronological File, 1981 June-July (Box 541, Folder 5585)
    - Marshall M. Bouton (MMB) - Chronological File, 1981 August-September (Box 541, Folder 5586)
    - Marshall M. Bouton (MMB) - Chronological File, 1981 October-November (Box 541, Folder 5587)
    - Marshall M. Bouton (MMB) - Chronological File, 1981 December (Box 541, Folder 5588)
    - Robert B. Oxnam- Asia Trip Diary, 1982 January 29-February 27 (Box 542, Folder 5589-5590)
    - Robert B. Oxnam - Social Functions, 1981 (Box 542, Folder 5591)
    - Chinatown planning council participant, 1982-1984 (Box 542, Folder 5592)
    - Stephanie Green - Director of Publications appointment, 1983 (Box 542, Folder 5593)
    - American Political Science Association Meeting, 1983 (Box 542, Folder 5594)
    - Marshall M. Bouton Calendars, 1981-1982 (Box 542, Folder 5595)
    - Asia Society - Annual Report - Program Lists, 1981-1982 (Box 542, Folder 5596)
    - Asia Magazine, coming articles, 1982-1983 (Box 542, Folder 5597)
    - Fox Butterfield Lecture on China, 1982 May 11 (Box 542, Folder 5598)
    - Thai Anniversary Programs, 1981-1982 (Box 543, Folder 5599)
    - Adam Malik luncheon, Washington Center, 1981 May 26 (Box 543, Folder 5600)
    - Program coordination issues, 1982 (Box 543, Folder 5601)
    - Australia Program, 1981 December 8 (Box 543, Folder 5602)
    - Hong Kong Mission Lucheon, 1981 December 1 (Box 543, Folder 5603)
    - Business Council Programs, 1981-1982 (Box 543, Folder 5604)
    - Munir P. Benjenk, Vice President, The World Bank, Reception, 1982 February 18 (Box 543, Folder 5605)
    - JDR 3rd Lectures, 1982 May 12 (Box 543, Folder 5606)
    - Luce Room Dedication-Watts Program, 1982 March 18 (Box 543, Folder 5607)
    - Visit of Indira Ganhdi, 1982 July-August (Box 543, Folder 5608)
    - Luncheon for Malaysian Prime Minister Mahatir, 1982 September 28 (Box 543, Folder 5609)
    - Disputes in Asia, 1982-83 (Box 543, Folder 5610)
    - MMB - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 548, Folder 5631)
    - MMB - Correspondence, 1982 January-March (Box 548, Folder 5632)
    - MMB - Correspondence, 1982 April-June (Box 548, Folder 5633)
    - MMB - Correspondence, 1982 July-October (Box 548, Folder 5634)
    - MMB - Correspondence, 1982 November-December (Box 548, Folder 5635)
    - Interoffice Memorandums to MMB, 1982-1983 (Box 548, Folder 5636)
    - Panel on South Asian Security Issues, 1981 June 4 (Box 549, Folder 5637)
    - Carnegie Endowment Conference - Indo-American Relations, 1982 June 26 (Box 549, Folder 5638)
    - MMB Calendar, 1981 August-1982 May (Box 549, Folder 5639)
    - Calendar - Roll over sheet of Events, 1981-1982 (Box 549, Folder 5640)
    - Public Affairs - Events - Weekly Roll over, 1981-1982 (Box 549, Folder 5641)
    - Department Heads Budget Exercise, 1982-1983 (Box 549, Folder 5642)
    - Public Affairs - Membership and special programs (Country Councils) - Monthly accounts, 1981-1982 (Box 549, Folder 5643)
    - Asian Agenda - Monthly Accounts, 1981-1982 (Box 549, Folder 5644)
    - Business Council - Monthly Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 549, Folder 5645)
    - ADSP - Monthly Accounts, 1981-1982 (Box 549, Folder 5646)
    - China Council - Monthly Accounts, 1981-1982 (Box 550, Folder 5647)
    - Public Affairs Department Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 550, Folder 5648)
    - Summary Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 550, Folder 5649)
    - Public Affairs - Directors Office Monthly Accounts, 1981-1982 (Box 550, Folder 5650)
    - Department Head Meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 550, Folder 5651)
    - Asia Society Financial Statement, 1981 June 30 (Box 550, Folder 5652)
    - Events - Calendars (Box 550, Folder 5653)
    - Asia Society Events - Weekly, 1981-1982 (Box 550, Folder 5654)
    - Asia Society - Notes - Background material (MMB), 1980 (Box 550, Folder 5655)
    - Asia Society - Monthly Calendar, 1981-1982 (Box 550, Folder 5656)
    - RBO Trip Letters, 1982 (Box 551, Folder 5657)
    - RBO Time Sheet, 1982 (Box 551, Folder 5658)
    - RBO Trip, 1982 February (Box 551, Folder 5659)
    - RBO - Indochina and North Korea Interest, 1982 (Box 551, Folder 5660)
    - RBO Correspondence, 1983 (Box 551, Folder 5661)
    - Asia Society-Fletcher Conference on Indonesia - Papers, 1983 October (Box 551, Folder 5662)
    - Advisory Group of the Asian Agenda Program, 1983 (Box 551, Folder 5663)
    - Public Affairs Advisory Structure (Box 551, Folder 5664)
    - Public Affairs Advisory Committee Meeting, 1981-1983 (Box 551, Folder 5665)
    - Public Affairs Advisory Committee at-large-members, 1981-1982 (Box 551, Folder 5666)
    - Area committee formation, 1981-1982 (Box 551, Folder 5667)
    - Public Affairs - Planning Meeting, 1982 March 17 (Box 551, Folder 5668)
    - Country Council Chairpersons Meeting, 1982 October 20 (Box 551, Folder 5669)
    - Asian Agenda Advisory Group Meeting, 1983 April 22 (Box 552, Folder 5670)
    - Business Programs - Background Materials, 1980-1982 (Box 552, Folder 5671)
    - Plans, 1982-1983 (Box 552, Folder 5672)
    - Public Affairs Plans - New directions, 1981 (Box 552, Folder 5673)
    - Correspondence, 1982 August (Box 552, Folder 5674)
    - Public Affairs - Program Plans, 1982-1983 (Box 552, Folder 5675)
    - Planning Meeting, 1982 March 17 (Box 552, Folder 5676)
    - Program Plans, 1982 Fall (Box 552, Folder 5677)
    - Public Affairs: Program Listings, 1982 (Box 552, Folder 5678)
    - Far East America Council (FEAC) - Merger, 1982 (Box 552, Folder 5679)
    - Asia Society - Budget Summary, 1982-1983 (Box 553, Folder 5680)
    - Gandhi Film Screening (Box 553, Folder 5681)
    - 1982-83 Annual Report Contributors, 1983 (Box 553, Folder 5682)
    - Williamsburg Conference XII, 1982 November 12-14 (Box 553, Folder 5683)